[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In December 2004, the discovery of the deepest coral reef in the United States was confirmed.  It is also the deepest coral reef in the world.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In domino, what does the term downing mean?", "correct_answer": "Putting the first tile of the game", "incorrect_answers": ["Branching the line of play", "Putting the last tile of the game", "Blocking another player"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the average weight of the Tasmanian Pygmy Possum?", "correct_answer": "About 7g", "incorrect_answers": ["About 250g", "About 50g", "About 100g"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor portrayed agent James Bond in the 1989 movie Licence to Kill?", "correct_answer": "Timothy Dalton", "incorrect_answers": ["Roger Moore", "Pierce Brosnan", "Sean Connery"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Astronauts age faster.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who won the Oscar for Best Actress in a Leading Role at the 72nd Academy Awards 2000?", "correct_answer": "Hilary Swank", "incorrect_answers": ["Meryl Streep", "Winona Ryder", "Julianne Moore"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If a prescription has the terms NS and OS written on it, what does this probably mean?", "correct_answer": "You have an eye problem.", "incorrect_answers": ["You need an IV.", "You cant get more of your ulcer medication.", "You have really bad dandruff."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the largest known pearl on the planet?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Pearl of Allah", "Pearl of Lao Tze", "Pearl of Lao Tzu"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Giraffes sometimes use their extremely long blue tongues for this purpose.", "correct_answer": "Cleaning insects from their face", "incorrect_answers": ["Stealing eggs from birds nests", "Playing games with other giraffes", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which character from the Star Wars saga first used the words May the Force be with you?", "correct_answer": "Obi-Wan Kenobi", "incorrect_answers": ["Princess Leia Organa", "Darth Vader", "Luke Skywalker"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The testes contain very fine coiled tubes known as the seminal vesicles.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many bones make up the backbone of a human baby?", "correct_answer": "33", "incorrect_answers": ["36", "24", "26"]}]